<NotepadPlus>
    <UserLang name="LilyPond" ext="ly" udlVersion="2.1">
        <Settings>
            <Global caseIgnored="no" allowFoldOfComments="no" foldCompact="no" forcePureLC="0" decimalSeparator="0" />
            <Prefix Keywords1="no" Keywords2="no" Keywords3="no" Keywords4="no" Keywords5="no" Keywords6="no" Keywords7="no" Keywords8="no" />
        </Settings>
        <KeywordLists>
            <Keywords name="Comments">00% ; 01 02 03%{ 04%}</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, prefix1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, prefix2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, extras1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, extras2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, suffix1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, suffix2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, range"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Operators1">&apos; , . ( ) # ~</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Operators2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, open">{ &lt;&lt; &lt;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, close">} &gt;&gt; &gt;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords1">\override \version \include \invalid \addquote \alternative \book \~ \mark \default \key \skip \octave \partial \time \change \consists \remove \accepts \defaultchild \denies \alias \type \description \name \context \grobdescriptions \markup \header \notemode \drummode \figuremode \chordmode \lyricmode \drums \figures \chords \lyrics \once \revert \set \unset \addlyrics \objectid \with \rest \paper \midi \layout \new \times \transpose \tag \relative \renameinput \repeat \lyricsto \score \sequential \simultaneous \longa \breve \maxima \tempo </Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords2">Forbid_line_break_engraver staff-symbol-referencer-interface clef-interface note-name-interface lyric-extender-interface mensural-ligature-interface Multi_measure_rest_engraver bass-figure-alignment-interface Slur_engraver Completion_heads_engraver rhythmic-grob-interface span-bar-interface Drum_note_performer InnerChoirStaff Score Bar_engraver Breathing_sign_engraver Staff spanner-interface Ligature_bracket_engraver Chord_name_engraver accidental-placement-interface Span_arpeggio_engraver MensuralVoice Stanza_number_engraver Grace_engraver Grace_beam_engraver script-interface Time_signature_engraver Stanza_number_align_engraver GregorianTranscriptionStaff Key_engraver cluster-beacon-interface TabVoice Dynamic_engraver rhythmic-head-interface Repeat_acknowledge_engraver dynamic-interface volta-bracket-interface bar-line-interface piano-pedal-interface font-interface VaticanaVoice staff-spacing-interface tie-interface Devnull dynamic-text-spanner-interface Script_row_engraver Stem_engraver grid-line-interface grob-interface custos-interface Font_size_engraver trill-pitch-accidental-interface Clef_engraver Text_engraver dynamic-line-spanner-interface Repeat_tie_engraver tablature-interface staff-symbol-interface rest-collision-interface Horizontal_bracket_engraver accidental-suggestion-interface Beam_performer Lyric_performer Piano_pedal_engraver vaticana-ligature-interface Tab_note_heads_engraver text-interface break-alignable-interface lyric-hyphen-interface grace-spacing-interface note-column-interface Vertical_align_engraver break-aligned-interface Staff_performer Ledger_line_engraver rest-interface Fingering_engraver figured-bass-continuation-interface metronome-mark-interface Key_performer Separating_line_group_engraver bend-after-interface DrumStaff unbreakable-spanner-interface trill-spanner-interface Grace_spacing_engraver Ambitus_engraver system-interface Swallow_engraver Cluster_spanner_engraver fret-diagram-interface gregorian-ligature-interface dots-interface percent-repeat-item-interface Time_signature_performer semi-tie-column-interface spacing-spanner-interface Staff_symbol_engraver mark-interface accidental-interface Text_spanner_engraver Swallow_performer system-start-text-interface Mensural_ligature_engraver chord-name-interface Lyric_engraver Translator script-column-interface Instrument_switch_engraver Grob_pq_engraver Volta_engraver breathing-sign-interface Span_bar_engraver Tab_harmonic_engraver Note_performer beam-interface note-collision-interface only-prebreak-interface stroke-finger-interface InnerStaffGroup tie-column-interface FretBoards Tie_engraver Laissez_vibrer_engraver slur-interface Custos_engraver Note_swallow_translator Rhythmic_column_engraver Default_bar_line_engraver note-spacing-interface FiguredBass vertically-spaceable-interface GregorianTranscriptionVoice stem-tremolo-interface measure-grouping-interface Spacing_engraver side-position-interface semi-tie-interface lyric-syllable-interface Engraver Pitched_trill_engraver ledger-line-spanner-interface stem-interface Extender_engraver Pitch_squash_engraver align-interface ambitus-interface Rest_swallow_translator string-number-interface self-alignment-interface Rest_collision_engraver hairpin-interface NoteNames Drum_notes_engraver arpeggio-interface Tweak_engraver ledgered-interface Global StaffGroup DrumVoice Voice GrandStaff Staff_collecting_engraver melody-spanner-interface Hara_kiri_engraver Figured_bass_position_engraver Tempo_performer New_dynamic_engraver Measure_grouping_engraver Hyphen_engraver Skip_event_swallow_translator Vaticana_ligature_engraver text-script-interface Tuplet_engraver Slur_performer spaceable-grob-interface Tie_performer Vertically_spaced_contexts_engraver Trill_spanner_engraver Spanner_break_forbid_engraver CueVoice ChoirStaff Glissando_engraver Balloon_engraver separation-item-interface Accidental_engraver Output_property_engraver hara-kiri-group-spanner-interface piano-pedal-script-interface system-start-delimiter-interface multi-measure-rest-interface Note_name_engraver Note_spacing_engraver Timing_translator Mark_engraver Control_track_performer Part_combine_engraver axis-group-interface note-head-interface horizontal-bracket-interface PianoStaff Slash_repeat_engraver Page_turn_engraver parentheses-interface key-signature-interface lyric-interface grid-point-interface item-interface Ottava_spanner_engraver Melody_engraver Percent_repeat_engraver tuplet-number-interface Rest_engraver stanza-number-interface enclosing-bracket-interface Break_align_engraver Piano_pedal_performer Paper_column_engraver pitched-trill-interface Grid_line_span_engraver Lyrics Instrument_name_engraver line-interface Bend_engraver Arpeggio_engraver key-cancellation-interface Grid_point_engraver Script_column_engraver Note_head_line_engraver spacing-options-interface Dot_column_engraver Chord_tremolo_engraver bass-figure-interface ottava-bracket-interface Bar_number_engraver Axis_group_engraver tuplet-bracket-interface Phrasing_slur_engraver Dynamic_align_engraver Piano_pedal_align_engraver Collision_engraver Dots_engraver New_fingering_engraver Figured_bass_engraver dot-column-interface multi-measure-interface Fretboard_engraver ligature-interface instrument-specific-markup-interface time-signature-interface Metronome_mark_engraver break-alignment-interface Auto_beam_engraver balloon-interface VaticanaStaff Script_engraver System_start_delimiter_engraver spacing-interface ligature-bracket-interface percent-repeat-interface ChordNames finger-interface TabStaff cluster-interface Beam_engraver RhythmicStaff String_number_engraver Dynamic_performer piano-pedal-bracket-interface Parenthesis_engraver Tab_staff_symbol_engraver paper-column-interface Note_heads_engraver MensuralStaff line-spanner-interface #:behaviour #:column #:condition #:depth #:exit-depth #:expression #:file-name #:file-regexp #:line #:procedure #:repeat-identical-behaviour #:single-shot #:skip-count $abs $acos $acosh $asin $asinh $atan $atan2 $atanh $cos $cosh $exp $expt $log $sin $sinh $sqrt $tan $tanh %library-dir %make-void-port %package-data-dir %read-delimited! %read-line %search-load-path %site-dir ,@ -&gt;char-set 1+ 1- &lt;apply-trap&gt; &lt;entry-trap&gt; &lt;exit-trap&gt; &lt;group&gt;-disable &lt;group&gt;-enable &lt;group&gt;-options &lt;group&gt;-set! &lt;location-trap&gt; &lt;procedure-trap&gt; &lt;source-trap&gt; &lt;step-trap&gt; &lt;trap&gt; abs accept access? acons acos acosh activate-readline add-duration add-duration! add-hook! alarm alist-&gt;hash-table alist-cons alist-copy alist-delete alist-delete! all-threads all-traps and and-let* angle any any-&gt;c32vector any-&gt;c64vector any-&gt;f32vector any-&gt;f64vector any-&gt;s16vector any-&gt;s32vector any-&gt;s64vector any-&gt;s8vector any-&gt;u16vector any-&gt;u32vector any-&gt;u64vector any-&gt;u8vector any-bits-set? append append! append-map append-map! append-reverse append-reverse! apply apply:nconc2last apropos-completion-function args-fold arithmetic-shift array-&gt;list array-contents array-copy! array-copy-in-order! array-dimensions array-equal? array-fill! array-for-each array-in-bounds? array-index-map! array-map! array-map-in-order! array-rank array-ref array-set! array-shape array-type array? ash asin asinh assoc assoc assoc-ref assoc-remove! assoc-set! assq assq-ref assq-remove! assq-set! assv assv-ref assv-remove! assv-set! async async-mark atan atanh backtrace backtrace basename begin begin-thread bind bind-textdomain-codeset bindtextdomain bit-count bit-count bit-count* bit-extract bit-field bit-invert! bit-position bit-set*! bit-set? bitvector bitvector-&gt;list bitvector-fill! bitvector-length bitvector-ref bitvector-set! bitvector? bitwise-and bitwise-if bitwise-ior bitwise-merge bitwise-not bitwise-xor boolean? booleans-&gt;integer break break break! broadcast-condition-variable bt c32vector c32vector-&gt;list c32vector-length c32vector-ref c32vector-set! c32vector? c64vector c64vector-&gt;list c64vector-length c64vector-ref c64vector-set! c64vector? caaaar caaadr caaar caadar caaddr caadr caar cadaar cadadr cadar caddar cadddr caddr cadr call-with-blocked-asyncs call-with-current-continuation call-with-input-file call-with-input-string call-with-new-thread call-with-output-file call-with-output-string call-with-unblocked-asyncs call-with-values call/cc car car+cdr case case-lambda catch cd cdaaar cdaadr cdaar cdadar cdaddr cdadr cdar cddaar cddadr cddar cdddar cddddr cdddr cddr cdr ceiling char-&gt;integer char-alphabetic? char-ci&lt;=? char-ci&lt;? char-ci=? char-ci&gt;=? char-ci&gt;? char-downcase char-is-both? char-lower-case? char-numeric? char-ready? char-set char-set-&gt;list char-set-&gt;string char-set-adjoin char-set-adjoin! char-set-any char-set-complement char-set-complement! char-set-contains? char-set-copy char-set-count char-set-cursor char-set-cursor-next char-set-delete char-set-delete! char-set-diff+intersection char-set-diff+intersection! char-set-difference char-set-difference! char-set-every char-set-filter char-set-filter! char-set-fold char-set-for-each char-set-hash char-set-intersection char-set-intersection! char-set-map char-set-ref char-set-size char-set-unfold char-set-unfold! char-set-union char-set-union! char-set-xor char-set-xor! char-set&lt;= char-set= char-set? char-upcase char-upper-case? char-whitespace? char&lt;=? char&lt;? char=? char&gt;=? char&gt;? char? chdir chmod chown chroot circular-list circular-list? close close-fdes close-input-port close-output-port close-pipe close-port closedir closure? command-line complex? concatenate concatenate! cond cond-expand condition condition-has-type? condition-message condition-ref condition-type? connect cons cons* cons-source continue continue copy-bit copy-bit-field copy-file copy-random-state copy-time copy-tree cos cosh count crypt ctermid current-date current-dynamic-state current-error-port current-error-port current-input-port current-input-port current-julian-day current-load-port current-modified-julian-day current-module current-output-port current-output-port current-thread current-time current-time cuserid cut cute date-&gt;julian-day date-&gt;modified-julian-day date-&gt;string date-&gt;time-monotonic date-&gt;time-tai date-&gt;time-utc date-day date-hour date-minute date-month date-nanosecond date-second date-week-day date-week-number date-year date-year-day date-zone-offset date? debug debug-disable debug-enable debug-object? debug-options debug-options-interface debug-set! debug-trap default-duplicate-binding-handler define define* define*-public define-condition-type define-macro define-module define-public define-reader-ctor define-record-type defined? defmacro defmacro* defmacro*-public delay delete delete delete! delete! delete-duplicates delete-duplicates! delete-file delete1! delq delq! delq1! delv delv! delv1! denominator deq! directory-stream? dirname display display-application display-backtrace display-error do dotted-list? doubly-weak-hash-table? down drain-input drop drop-right drop-right! drop-while dup dup-&gt;fdes dup-&gt;inport dup-&gt;outport dup-&gt;port dup2 duplicate-port dynamic-args-call dynamic-call dynamic-func dynamic-link dynamic-object? dynamic-state? dynamic-unlink dynamic-wind effective-version eighth enclose-array end-of-char-set? endgrent endhostent endnetent endprotoent endpwent endservent enq! entity? environ eof-object? eq? equal? eqv? error error? eval eval-disable eval-enable eval-options eval-options-interface eval-options-interface eval-set! eval-string evaluate evaluator-traps-interface evaluator-traps-interface even? every exact-&gt;inexact exact? execl execle execlp exp expect expect-strings export expt extract-condition f32vector f32vector-&gt;list f32vector-length f32vector-ref f32vector-set! f32vector? f64vector f64vector-&gt;list f64vector-length f64vector-ref f64vector-set! f64vector? false-if-exception fchmod fchown fcntl fdes-&gt;inport fdes-&gt;outport fdes-&gt;ports fdopen feature? fflush fifth file-exists? file-port? filename-completion-function fileno filter filter! filter-map find find-tail finish first first-set-bit flock floor fluid-ref fluid-set! fluid? flush-all-ports fn fold fold-matches fold-right for-each for-each force force-output format fourth frame frame-arguments frame-evaluating-args? frame-next frame-number frame-overflow? frame-previous frame-procedure frame-procedure? frame-real? frame-source frame? fstat fsync ftell ftruncate ftw gc gc-live-object-stats gc-stats gcd gds-apropos gds-complete-symbol gds-debug-trap gds-down gds-eval-defun gds-eval-expression gds-eval-last-sexp gds-eval-region gds-evaluate gds-frame-args gds-frame-info gds-go gds-help-symbol gds-proc-source gds-select-stack-frame gds-step-file gds-step-into gds-step-over gds-up generalized-vector-&gt;list generalized-vector-length generalized-vector-ref generalized-vector-set! generalized-vector? gensym get-internal-real-time get-internal-run-time get-output-string get-print-state get-trap getcwd getegid getenv geteuid getgid getgr getgrent getgrgid getgrnam getgroups gethost gethostbyaddr gethostbyname gethostent gethostname getitimer getlogin getnet getnetbyaddr getnetbyname getnetent getopt-long getpass getpeername getpgrp getpid getppid getpriority getproto getprotobyname getprotobynumber getprotoent getpw getpwent getpwnam getpwuid getserv getservbyname getservbyport getservent getsockname getsockopt getter-with-setter gettext gettimeofday getuid GH_ALLOW_INTS gh_append gh_append2 gh_append3 gh_append4 gh_apply gh_assoc gh_assq gh_assv gh_bool2scm gh_boolean_p gh_c gh_call0 gh_call1 gh_call2 gh_call3 gh_car gh_catch gh_cdr gh_char2scm gh_char_p gh_chars2byvect gh_cons GH_DEFER_INTS gh_define gh_double2scm gh_doubles2dvect gh_doubles2scm gh_enter gh_eq_p gh_equal_p gh_eqv_p gh_eval_file gh_eval_str gh_exact_p gh_floats2fvect gh_get_substr gh_inexact_p gh_ints2scm gh_is_eq gh_is_equal gh_is_eqv gh_length gh_list gh_list_p gh_list_ref gh_list_tail gh_list_to_vector gh_load gh_long2scm gh_longs2ivect gh_make_vector gh_member gh_memq gh_memv gh_new_procedure gh_null_p gh_obj_length gh_pair_p gh_procedure_p gh_repl gh_reverse gh_scm2bool gh_scm2char gh_scm2chars gh_scm2double gh_scm2doubles gh_scm2floats gh_scm2long gh_scm2longs gh_scm2newstr gh_scm2shorts gh_scm2ulong gh_set_car_x gh_set_cdr_x gh_set_substr gh_shorts2svect gh_str02scm gh_str2scm gh_string_equal_p gh_symbol2newstr gh_symbol2scm gh_symbol_p gh_throw gh_ulong2scm gh_ulongs2uvect gh_vector gh_vector_length gh_vector_p gh_vector_ref gh_vector_set gmtime group:gid group:mem group:name group:passwd GUILE_CHECK_RETVAL GUILE_FLAGS GUILE_MODULE_AVAILABLE GUILE_MODULE_CHECK GUILE_MODULE_EXPORTS GUILE_MODULE_REQUIRED GUILE_MODULE_REQUIRED_EXPORT GUILE_PROGS GUILE_SITE_DIR hash hash hash-by-identity hash-clear! hash-create-handle! hash-fold hash-for-each hash-for-each-handle hash-get-handle hash-map-&gt;list hash-ref hash-remove! hash-set! hash-table-&gt;alist hash-table-delete! hash-table-equivalence-function hash-table-exists? hash-table-fold hash-table-hash-function hash-table-keys hash-table-ref hash-table-ref/default hash-table-set! hash-table-size hash-table-update! hash-table-update!/default hash-table-values hash-table-walk hash-table? hashq hashq-create-handle! hashq-get-handle hashq-ref hashq-remove! hashq-set! hashv hashv-create-handle! hashv-get-handle hashv-ref hashv-remove! hashv-set! hashx-create-handle! hashx-get-handle hashx-ref hashx-remove! hashx-set! hook-&gt;list hook-empty? hook? hostent:addr-list hostent:addrtype hostent:aliases hostent:length hostent:name htonl htons if imag-part inet-aton inet-lnaof inet-makeaddr inet-netof inet-ntoa inet-ntop inet-pton inexact-&gt;exact inexact? inf inf? info args info frame input-port? install-trap integer-&gt;char integer-&gt;list integer-expt integer-length integer? interaction-environment iota isatty? join-thread julian-day-&gt;date julian-day-&gt;time-monotonic julian-day-&gt;time-tai julian-day-&gt;time-utc key keyword-&gt;string keyword-&gt;symbol keyword? keyword? kill lambda lambda* last last-pair last-stack-frame lazy-catch lchown lcm length length+ let let* let*-values let-keywords let-keywords* let-optional let-optional* let-values letpar letrec link list list-&gt;array list-&gt;bitvector list-&gt;c32vector list-&gt;c64vector list-&gt;char-set list-&gt;char-set! list-&gt;f32vector list-&gt;f64vector list-&gt;integer list-&gt;s16vector list-&gt;s32vector list-&gt;s64vector list-&gt;s8vector list-&gt;stream list-&gt;string list-&gt;typed-array list-&gt;u16vector list-&gt;u32vector list-&gt;u64vector list-&gt;u8vector list-&gt;vector list-&gt;weak-vector list-cdr-ref list-cdr-set! list-copy list-copy list-head list-index list-matches list-ref list-set! list-tabulate list-tail list-traps list= list? listen load load-extension load-from-path local-eval localtime lock-mutex log log10 log2-binary-factors logand logbit? logcount logior lognot logtest logxor lset-adjoin lset-diff+intersection lset-diff+intersection! lset-difference lset-difference! lset-intersection lset-intersection! lset-union lset-union! lset-xor lset-xor! lset&lt;= lset= lstat macro-name macro-transformer macro-type macro? magnitude main_prog major-version make-arbiter make-array make-bitvector make-buffered-input-port make-c32vector make-c64vector make-class-object make-completion-function make-compound-condition make-condition make-condition-type make-condition-variable make-date make-doubly-weak-hash-table make-dynamic-state make-f32vector make-f64vector make-fluid make-guardian make-hash-table make-hash-table make-hook make-line-buffered-input-port make-list make-mutex make-object-property make-parameter make-polar make-procedure-with-setter make-q make-record-type make-rectangular make-recursive-mutex make-regexp make-s16vector make-s32vector make-s64vector make-s8vector make-shared-array make-socket-address make-soft-port make-stack make-stream make-string make-struct make-struct-layout make-subclass-object make-symbol make-thread make-time make-typed-array make-u16vector make-u32vector make-u64vector make-u8vector make-undefined-variable make-variable make-vector make-vtable make-vtable-vtable make-weak-key-hash-table make-weak-value-hash-table make-weak-vector malloc-stats map map map! map-in-order match:count match:end match:prefix match:start match:string match:substring match:suffix max member member memoized-environment memoized? memq memv merge merge! message-condition? micro-version min minor-version mkdir mknod mkstemp! mktime modified-julian-day-&gt;date modified-julian-day-&gt;time-monotonic modified-julian-day-&gt;time-tai modified-julian-day-&gt;time-utc module-use! modulo modulo-expt monitor move-&gt;fdes n-for-each-par-map n-par-for-each n-par-map nan nan? negative? netent:addrtype netent:aliases netent:name netent:net newline next nftw ngettext nice nil-car nil-cdr nil-cons nil-eq ninth not not-pair? ntohl ntohs null null-environment null-list? null? number-&gt;string number? numerator object-&gt;string object-properties object-property odd? open open-fdes open-file open-input-file open-input-output-pipe open-input-pipe open-input-string open-output-file open-output-pipe open-output-string open-pipe open-pipe* opendir operator? option option-names option-optional-arg? option-processor option-ref option-required-arg? or output-port? pair-fold pair-fold-right pair-for-each pair? par-for-each par-map parallel parameterize parse-path partition partition! passwd:dir passwd:gecos passwd:gid passwd:name passwd:passwd passwd:shell passwd:uid pause pclose peek-char pipe PKG_CHECK_MODULES popen port-&gt;fdes port-&gt;stream port-closed? port-column port-filename port-for-each port-line port-mode port-mode port-revealed port-with-print-state port? position positive? pretty-print primitive-_exit primitive-eval primitive-exit primitive-fork primitive-load primitive-load-path primitive-make-property primitive-move-&gt;fdes primitive-property-del! primitive-property-ref primitive-property-set! print-disable print-enable print-options print-options-interface print-options-interface print-set! procedure procedure-&gt;macro procedure-&gt;memoizing-macro procedure-&gt;syntax procedure-documentation procedure-environment procedure-name procedure-properties procedure-property procedure-source procedure-with-setter? procedure? program-arguments promise? proper-list? protoent:aliases protoent:name protoent:proto provide provided? PTR2SCM putenv pwd q-empty-check q-empty? q-front q-length q-pop! q-push! q-rear q-remove! q? quasiquote quit quote quotient raise random random:exp random:hollow-sphere! random:normal random:normal-vector! random:solid-sphere! random:uniform rational? rationalize re-export read read-char read-delimited read-delimited! read-disable read-disable read-enable read-enable read-hash-extend read-line read-line! read-options read-options read-options-interface read-options-interface read-set! read-set! read-string!/partial readdir readline readline-disable readline-enable readline-options readline-port readline-set! readlink real-part real? rec receive record-accessor record-constructor record-modifier record-predicate record-type-descriptor record-type-fields record-type-name record? recv! recvfrom! redirect-port reduce reduce-right regexp-exec regexp-match? regexp-quote regexp-substitute regexp-substitute/global regexp? release-arbiter release-port-handle remainder remove remove! remove-hook! rename rename-file require require-extension reset-hook! resolve-interface resolve-module restore-signals restricted-vector-sort! reverse reverse! reverse-bit-field reverse-list-&gt;string rewinddir rmdir rotate-bit-field round run-asyncs run-hook s16vector s16vector-&gt;list s16vector-length s16vector-ref s16vector-set! s16vector? s32vector s32vector-&gt;list s32vector-length s32vector-ref s32vector-set! s32vector? s64vector s64vector-&gt;list s64vector-length s64vector-ref s64vector-set! s64vector? s8vector s8vector-&gt;list s8vector-length s8vector-ref s8vector-set! s8vector? save-module-excursion scheme-report-environment search-path second seed-&gt;random-state seek select send sendto serious-condition? servent:aliases servent:name servent:port servent:proto set-buffered-input-continuation?! set-car! set-cdr! set-current-dynamic-state set-current-error-port set-current-input-port set-current-module set-current-output-port set-object-procedure! set-object-properties! set-object-property! set-port-column! set-port-filename! set-port-line! set-port-revealed! set-procedure-properties! set-procedure-property! set-program-arguments set-readline-input-port! set-readline-output-port! set-readline-prompt! set-source-properties! set-source-property! set-struct-vtable-name! set-symbol-property! set-time-nanosecond! set-time-second! set-time-type! set-tm:gmtoff set-tm:hour set-tm:isdst set-tm:mday set-tm:min set-tm:mon set-tm:sec set-tm:wday set-tm:yday set-tm:year set-tm:zone set-trace-layout set! setegid setenv seteuid setgid setgr setgrent setgroups sethost sethostent sethostname setitimer setlocale setnet setnetent setpgid setpriority setproto setprotoent setpw setpwent setserv setservent setsid setsockopt setter setuid setvbuf seventh shared-array-increments shared-array-offset shared-array-root shutdown sigaction signal-condition-variable simple-format sin sinh sixth sleep sloppy-assoc sloppy-assq sloppy-assv sockaddr:addr sockaddr:fam sockaddr:flowinfo sockaddr:path sockaddr:port sockaddr:scopeid socket socketpair sort sort! sort-list sort-list! sorted? source-properties source-property span span! split-at split-at! sqrt stable-sort stable-sort! stack-id stack-length stack-ref stack? start-stack stat stat:atime stat:blksize stat:blocks stat:ctime stat:dev stat:gid stat:ino stat:mode stat:mtime stat:nlink stat:perms stat:rdev stat:size stat:type stat:uid status:exit-val status:stop-sig status:term-sig step stream-&gt;list stream-&gt;list&amp;length stream-&gt;reversed-list stream-&gt;reversed-list&amp;length stream-&gt;vector stream-car stream-cdr stream-fold stream-for-each stream-map stream-null? strerror strftime string string-&gt;char-set string-&gt;char-set! string-&gt;date string-&gt;keyword string-&gt;list string-&gt;number string-&gt;symbol string-any string-append string-append/shared string-capitalize string-capitalize! string-ci-&gt;symbol string-ci-hash string-ci&lt; string-ci&lt;= string-ci&lt;=? string-ci&lt;&gt; string-ci&lt;? string-ci= string-ci=? string-ci&gt; string-ci&gt;= string-ci&gt;=? string-ci&gt;? string-compare string-compare-ci string-concatenate string-concatenate-reverse string-concatenate-reverse/shared string-concatenate/shared string-contains string-contains-ci string-copy string-copy! string-count string-delete string-downcase string-downcase! string-drop string-drop-right string-every string-fill! string-filter string-fold string-fold-right string-for-each string-for-each-index string-hash string-hash string-hash-ci string-index string-index-right string-join string-length string-map string-map! string-match string-null? string-pad string-pad-right string-prefix-ci? string-prefix-length string-prefix-length-ci string-prefix? string-ref string-replace string-reverse string-reverse! string-rindex string-set! string-skip string-skip-right string-split string-suffix-ci? string-suffix-length string-suffix-length-ci string-suffix? string-tabulate string-take string-take-right string-titlecase string-titlecase! string-tokenize string-trim string-trim-both string-trim-right string-unfold string-unfold-right string-upcase string-upcase! string-xcopy! string&lt; string&lt;= string&lt;=? string&lt;&gt;&gt; string&lt;? string= string=? string&gt; string&gt;= string&gt;=? string&gt;? string? strptime struct-ref struct-set! struct-vtable struct-vtable-name struct-vtable-tag struct-vtable? struct? substring substring-fill! substring-move! substring/copy substring/read-only substring/shared subtract-duration subtract-duration! symbol-&gt;keyword symbol-&gt;string symbol-fref symbol-fset! symbol-hash symbol-interned? symbol-pref symbol-prefix-proc symbol-property symbol-property-remove! symbol-pset! symbol? symlink sync sync-q! system system* system-async-mark system-error-errno take take! take-right take-while take-while! tan tanh tc:depth tc:frame tc:real-depth tc:return-value tc:stack tc:type tcgetpgrp tcsetpgrp tenth textdomain third thread-exited? throw thunk? time-difference time-difference! time-monotonic-&gt;date time-monotonic-&gt;time-tai time-monotonic-&gt;time-tai! time-monotonic-&gt;time-utc time-monotonic-&gt;time-utc! time-nanosecond time-resolution time-second time-tai-&gt;date time-tai-&gt;julian-day time-tai-&gt;modified-julian-day time-tai-&gt;time-monotonic time-tai-&gt;time-monotonic! time-tai-&gt;time-utc time-tai-&gt;time-utc! time-type time-utc-&gt;date time-utc-&gt;julian-day time-utc-&gt;modified-julian-day time-utc-&gt;time-monotonic time-utc-&gt;time-monotonic! time-utc-&gt;time-tai time-utc-&gt;time-tai! time&lt;=? time&lt;? time=? time&gt;=? time&gt;? time? times tm:gmtoff tm:hour tm:isdst tm:mday tm:min tm:mon tm:sec tm:wday tm:yday tm:year tm:zone tmpnam tms:clock tms:cstime tms:cutime tms:stime tms:utime trace trace-at-exit trace-port trace-trap trace-until-exit trace/info trace/pid trace/real? trace/source trace/source-column trace/source-file-name trace/source-line trace/stack trace/stack-depth trace/stack-id trace/stack-real-depth trace/type transpose-array trap-disable trap-disable trap-enable trap-enable trap-here trap-set! trap-set! traps traps truncate truncate truncate-file try-arbiter try-mutex ttyname typed-array? tzset u16vector u16vector-&gt;list u16vector-length u16vector-ref u16vector-set! u16vector? u32vector u32vector-&gt;list u32vector-length u32vector-ref u32vector-set! u32vector? u64vector u64vector-&gt;list u64vector-length u64vector-ref u64vector-set! u64vector? u8vector u8vector-&gt;list u8vector-length u8vector-ref u8vector-set! u8vector? ucs-range-&gt;char-set ucs-range-&gt;char-set! umask uname unfold unfold-right uniform-array-read! uniform-array-write uniform-vector-&gt;list uniform-vector-length uniform-vector-read! uniform-vector-ref uniform-vector-set! uniform-vector-write uniform-vector? uninstall-trap unlink unlock-mutex unmemoize unquote unquote-splicing unread-char unread-char unread-string unread-string unsetenv untrace unzip1 unzip2 unzip3 unzip4 unzip5 up use-modules use-syntax usleep utime utsname:machine utsname:nodename utsname:release utsname</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords3">\AncientRemoveEmptyStaffContext \RemoveEmptyRhythmicStaffContext \RemoveEmptyStaffContext \accent \aeolian \afterGraceFraction \aikenHeads \arpeggio \arpeggioArrowDown \arpeggioArrowUp \arpeggioBracket \arpeggioNormal \arpeggioParenthesis \autoBeamOff \autoBeamOn \balloonLengthOff \balloonLengthOn \bassFigureExtendersOff \bassFigureExtendersOn \bassFigureStaffAlignmentDown \bassFigureStaffAlignmentNeutral \bassFigureStaffAlignmentUp \between-system-padding \between-system-space \bigger \blackTriangleMarkup \bookTitleMarkup \bracketCloseSymbol \bracketOpenSymbol \break \breve \cadenzaOff \cadenzaOn \center \chordmodifiers \cm \coda \compressFullBarRests \cr \cresc \crescHairpin \crescTextCresc \decr \defaultTimeSignature \dim \dimHairpin \dimTextDecr \dimTextDecresc \dimTextDim \dorian \dotsDown \dotsNeutral \dotsUp \down \downbow \downmordent \downprall \drumPitchNames \dutchPitchnames \dynamicDown \dynamicNeutral \dynamicUp \easyHeadsOff \easyHeadsOn \endcr \endcresc \enddecr \enddim \endincipit \escapedBiggerSymbol \escapedExclamationSymbol \escapedParenthesisCloseSymbol \escapedParenthesisOpenSymbol \escapedSmallerSymbol \espressivo \evenHeaderMarkup \expandFullBarRests \f \fermata \fermataMarkup \ff \fff \ffff \first-page-number \flageolet \fp \frenchChords \fullJazzExceptions \fz \germanChords \glissando \harmonic \hideNotes \hideStaffSwitch \huge \ignatzekExceptionMusic \ignatzekExceptions \improvisationOff \improvisationOn \in \instrument-definitions \ionian \italianChords \laissezVibrer \large \left \lheel \lineprall \locrian \longa \longfermata \ltoe \lydian \major \marcato \maxima \melisma \melismaEnd \mergeDifferentlyDottedOff \mergeDifferentlyDottedOn \mergeDifferentlyHeadedOff \mergeDifferentlyHeadedOn \mf \midiDrumPitches \minor \mixolydian \mm \mordent \mp \newSpacingSection \noBeam \noBreak \normalsize \numericTimeSignature \oddFooterMarkup \oddHeaderMarkup \oneVoice \open \output-scale \p \page-limit-inter-system-space \page-top-space \parenthesisCloseSymbol \parenthesisOpenSymbol \partialJazzExceptions \partialJazzMusic \phrasingSlurDashed \phrasingSlurDotted \phrasingSlurDown \phrasingSlurNeutral \phrasingSlurSolid \phrasingSlurUp \phrygian \pipeSymbol \pitchnames \portato \pp \ppp \pppp \ppppp \prall \pralldown \prallmordent \prallprall \prallup \predefinedFretboardsOff \predefinedFretboardsOn \print-first-page-number \print-page-number \pt \ragged-bottom \ragged-last-bottom \repeatTie \reverseturn \rfz \rheel \right \rtoe \sacredHarpHeads \scoreTitleMarkup \segno \semiGermanChords \setDefaultDurationToQuarter \sf \sff \sfp \sfz \shiftOff \shiftOn \shiftOnn \shiftOnnn \shortfermata \showStaffSwitch \signumcongruentiae \slashSeparator \slurDashed \slurDotted \slurDown \slurNeutral \slurSolid \slurUp \small \smaller \sostenutoOff \sostenutoOn \sp \spp \staccatissimo \staccato \start \startAcciaccaturaMusic \startAppoggiaturaMusic \startGraceMusic \startGroup \startStaff \startTextSpan \startTrillSpan \stemDown \stemNeutral \stemUp \stop \stopAcciaccaturaMusic \stopAppoggiaturaMusic \stopGraceMusic \stopGroup \stopStaff \stopTextSpan \stopTrillSpan \stopped \sustainOff \sustainOn \tagline \teeny \tenuto \textLengthOff \textLengthOn \textSpannerDown \textSpannerNeutral \textSpannerUp \thumb \tieDashed \tieDotted \tieDown \tieNeutral \tieSolid \tieUp \tildeSymbol \tiny \tocItemMarkup \tocTitleMarkup \treCorde \trill \tupletDown \tupletNeutral \tupletUp \turn \unHideNotes \unaCorda \unit \up \upbow \upmordent \upprall \varcoda \verylongfermata \voiceFour \voiceFourStyle \voiceNeutralStyle \voiceOne \voiceOneStyle \voiceThree \voiceThreeStyle \voiceTwo \voiceTwoStyle \whiteTriangleMarkup \acciaccatura \addChordShape \addInstrumentDefinition \addQuote \afterGrace \allowPageTurn \applyContext \applyMusic \applyOutput \appoggiatura \assertBeamQuant \assertBeamSlope \autochange \balloonGrobText \balloonText \bar \barNumberCheck \bendAfter \breathe \clef \cueDuring \displayLilyMusic \displayMusic \endSpanners \featherDurations \grace \includePageLayoutFile \instrumentSwitch \keepWithTag \killCues \label \makeClusters \musicMap \noPageBreak \noPageTurn \octaveCheck \oldaddlyrics \ottava \overrideProperty \pageBreak \pageTurn \parallelMusic \parenthesize \partcombine \pitchedTrill \pointAndClickOff \pointAndClickOn \quoteDuring \removeWithTag \resetRelativeOctave \rightHandFinger \scaleDurations \scoreTweak \shiftDurations \spacingTweaks \storePredefinedDiagram \tag \tocItem \transposedCueDuring \transposition \tweak \unfoldRepeats \withMusicProperty </Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords4">\abs-fontsize \arrow-head \backslashed-digit \beam \bold \box \bracket \caps \center-align \center-column \char \circle \column \combine \concat \dir-column \doubleflat \doublesharp \draw-circle \draw-line \dynamic \epsfile \fill-line \filled-box \finger \flat \fontCaps \fontsize \fraction \fret-diagram \fret-diagram-terse \fret-diagram-verbose \fromproperty \general-align \halign \harp-pedal \hbracket \hcenter-in \hspace \huge \italic \justify \justify-field \justify-string \large \larger \left-align \left-column \line \lookup \lower \magnify \markalphabet \markletter \medium \musicglyph \natural \normal-size-sub \normal-size-super \normal-text \normalsize \note \note-by-number \null \number \on-the-fly \override \pad-around \pad-markup \pad-to-box \pad-x \page-ref \postscript \put-adjacent \raise \right-align \right-column \roman \rotate \rounded-box \sans \score \semiflat \semisharp \sesquiflat \sesquisharp \sharp \simple \slashed-digit \small \smallCaps \smaller \stencil \strut \sub \super \teeny \text \tied-lyric \tiny \translate \translate-scaled \transparent \triangle \typewriter \underline \upright \vcenter \verbatim-file \whiteout \with-color \with-dimensions \with-url \wordwrap \wordwrap-field \wordwrap-string </Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords5"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords6"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords7"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords8"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Delimiters">00&quot; 01 02&quot; 03 04 05 06 07 08 09 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 </Keywords>
        </KeywordLists>
        <Styles>
            <WordsStyle name="DEFAULT" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="COMMENTS" fgColor="C80000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="LINE COMMENTS" fgColor="C80000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="NUMBERS" fgColor="FF0000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS1" fgColor="004080" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="1" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS2" fgColor="008000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="1" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS3" fgColor="0080FF" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="1" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS4" fgColor="804000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="1" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS5" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS6" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS7" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS8" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="OPERATORS" fgColor="0000A0" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN CODE1" fgColor="0000FF" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN CODE2" fgColor="0000FF" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN COMMENT" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS1" fgColor="FF0080" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS2" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS3" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="Lucida Console" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS4" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS5" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS6" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS7" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS8" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="REGEX" fgColor="8000FF" bgColor="F2F4FF" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
        </Styles>
    </UserLang>
</NotepadPlus>
